foreign
[Music]
Dubai recently and captured our
experience through our vlog
[Music]
we booked Emirates flight ek517 from
Delhi Terminal 3 airport award flight
departed at evening 4 15 pm and we reach
Dubai at 6 30 PM UAE time
total cost round trip in Emirates flight
for two people was rupees 51 500 and we
booked the flight one and a half months
proud to our journey
we applied for his way 30 days
to our journey total Visa fees for two
person was 12 600 rupees inclusive
for Visa we had to upload our flight
tickets and hotel booking voucher our
e-visa was approved within seven days of
our application and we received it via
email
we bought a travel insurance from ICICI
Lombard
worth rupees 917 for two persons since
we traveled on Emirates flight we were
not required to fill any declaration
form
however we filled the air should be the
Declaration from as a protocol for our
return Journey from Dubai to
[Music]
India's Terminal 3 of Dubai
International Airport the immigration
was really smooth and completed in 10
minutes Dubai is well connected through
metro line we took Metro from terminal 3
station to reach Union Metro station via
red line from Union Metro we
interchanged and took another Metro to
paneer Square Metro Station
[Music]
next morning we went to Dubai Mall after
having breakfast we walked from our
hotel to baniard square Metro Station
we boarded the we then off-boarded at
Union Metro Station from Union Metro we
took another Metro to Dubai Mall Metro
Station
[Music]
we roamed around in Dubai Mall which is
situated in downtown Dubai
[Music]
after exploring Dubai Mall we went to
visit Dubai aquarium and underwater zoo
in the afternoon
there was a lot of Rush at the booking
counter
we had already booked our Aquarium
tickets from thrillophilia
which included access to the aquarium
tunnel access to the underwater zoo and
class bottom boat tour
total ticket cost for two percent was
rupees
4950 which equivalates to
237 AED
at the booking counter
ticket for one person was 300 AED
which comes out to be rupees six to
seven zero per person so it is it is
advisable that all tourists going to
aquarium should book their tickets prior
to at any online website third party
the aquarium is open from 10 AM in the
morning till 11 pm at night from Monday
to Thursday and from 10 AM till midnight
on Friday till Saturday Friday till
Sunday
[Music]
thank you
as we walked into the aquarium tunnel it
was really a surreal and fascinating to
see 270 degree experience for us
we watched various marine species
including sharks fishes manta rays in a
near perfect detail
the 48 meter long aquarium tunnel
took us 11 meter under surface
[Music]
thank you
after completing the tunnel walk we came
to the level 2 which is the underwater
zoo we walked across three ecological
zones which are rainforest Rocky Shore
and living ocean we saw different types
of fishes jellyfish seahorses spider
crabs piranha and anchor fish
foreign
[Music]
thank you
we also saw crocodiles Garden eels petal
fish catfish in more than 40 aquatic
displays
after completing the zoo tour we went
for the glass bottom boat tour the glass
bottom 2 allowed us to witness the Dubai
aquarium tank
which is one of the largest suspended
aquarium tank in the world
a 10 million liter Dubai aquarium tank
has more than 300 sharks including sand
tiger sharks and manta rays and we were
lucky to see few of them right below us
through the glass bottom
boat
[Music]
took three hours to complete we were
tired and hungry at the same time we
went the food court of the Dubai Mall
and had burger from Wendy's and relax
for some time the Dubai Mall is really
huge and one needs to relax and explode
to ensure not getting tired too easily
[Music]
we downloaded a scale app from Google
Play Store that helped us in traveling
across Dubai it shows the routes and
availability of public transport mode
such as bus metro train
tram taxis Etc
[Music]
thank you
in the evening we went to see the Burj
Khalifa which is the tallest building in
the world and one of the main
attractions of Dubai Burj Khalifa has
over 160 stories
and has a height of 828 meters we were
really mesmerized by the Grandeur of
Burj Khalifa till that date he had only
seen it in pictures and videos but
seeing it right in front of her eyes was
definitely one of the best moments of a
Dubai trip
however we keep going to the top of Burj
Khalifa level 124 and 125 and instead
enjoyed the sunset view at Waterfront
Palm Promenade in the Dubai Mall the
ticket for enjoying panoramic views from
the level 124 and 125 in Burj Khalifa
starts from 169 Dirham per person and it
goes up to 244 Dirham for evening slots
panoramic levels are open from 8 am in
the morning till 10 pm at night every
day
[Music]
in evening from 6 PM onwards we watch
Dubai fountain show
Dubai fountain show is on the Burj
Khalifa Lake which sits between Dubai
Mall sukh al-bahar and Burj Khalifa
the crowd peaked and we were fortunate
to get a good place to view the fountain
show
at the waterfront prominent the show
happens from 6 PM till 11 pm every day
at an interval of 30 minutes
it is advisable for people to stand at
The prominent 15 minutes before the show
[Music]
water will start to twinkle 10 minutes
for and prominent lights are dim
eventually
[Music]
after the fountain show we also watch
the
laser light show on Burj Khalifa The
Experience was really great the laser
show at Burj Khalifa starts from 7 30 pm
and goes up till 11 30 P.M to 10 in
terms of 30 minutes
if you guys are lucky you can witness
special things Lighting on Burj Khalifa
for National and
foreign
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
thank you
we returned back from Dubai Mall and
took a Metro to reach pania metro metro
station
we had dinner consisting of chicken
biryani and mutton Rogan Josh from
parklieri restaurant in Dera banaya
Square Park Leary is a famous restaurant
in Old Dubai and serves one of the best
Biryani in Dubai and Dera region
that's the end of our day one at Dubai
and hope you like our video please do
comment and share it among your friends
and family and subscribe to our Channel
and stay tuned for more Vlogs on Dubai
in our upcoming days